Hello.
I'm really sorry.
The restaurant was late preparing the food.
I might be a few minutes late.
Can I confirm the delivery in advance?
Otherwise, I'll be fined.
No, no, no. Yes, yes.
I'm delivering your order first right now.
Hello?
Please don't be mad.
I'll be right there, okay?
I'm only two kilometers away.
No.
P-Please don't be mad.
I... I really...
They were late making it.
It's not my fault.
I'll be right there, okay?
Get up!
Get up! Fight back!
No.
I won't fight back.
I came here today to take a beating.
Fine.
Then I won't hold back.
Still afraid to die, huh?
For all these years,
I've been repenting.
You...
You repenting?
What the hell good is your repenting?!
Where were you back then?!
I went to the hospital back then.
You just didn't know.
These are
the flowers I delivered to this bed.
Who sent them?
I... I don't know.
My colleague transferred the order to me.
Do I know you?
You've delivered food to our house before.
Yeah.
I deliver to that whole area.
If there's nothing else,
I'll get going.
Wait a minute.
What's this?
You're the rider who ran the red light.
This is all my savings.
I'm sorry.
Zhang Ya never told me.
She told me not to tell you.
She said you would never forgive me.
And she forgave you?
I... I don't know.
We only met that one time.
She told me never to go back.
No, no.
I don't get it.
Why did you go see her?
None of the security cameras caught you.
We didn't know what you looked like.
Don't lie.
Because you treated me so well.
What did you say?
I wear a sweater under my shirt to keep warm.
The thing is, it scratches my neck.
Just give me this one.
All the male celebrities dress like this now.
How come I've never seen any male celebrity dress like this?
That delivery is ours, right?
I think so.
Sir.
Unit 1, 502.
Right.
This is mine.
No.
0223.
My last name is Xie.
Okay. No.
Let me carry it for you. It's pretty heavy.
It's fine.
Thanks a lot.
Thanks then.
No problem. Bye.
Bye.
Look at his leg.
Sir.
What is it?
Here.
Take this.
No, no, no.
I don't want it. No, no.
Just take it, take it. It's fine.
The roads are slippery in the rain.
Stay safe.
Alright, thanks.
Alright, goodbye.
Goodbye.
Take it slow, Sir.
Thanks.
Friendly reminder.
One minute left in this round.
Hit me now, or it'll be too late.
Only one minute left. Don't worry.
I definitely won't dodge this time.
Move, move, move!
Mr. Xie, only one minute left.
I forfeit! I forfeit!
You...
You're sparing me.
It's what my wife wanted.
The match is over.
There are no losers in this round either.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
Thank whoever you should. Now go.
Okay.
Fun, fun, fun.
It's the final round.
Will you let me go after this?
Of course.
But there's an additional rule this round.
You can't forfeit.
The penalty for failing is also a bit harsher.
Which is...
electrocuting me, right?
Who are you?
I'm Xie Xin.
And who are you?
Wait, wait, wait.
This is a bit confusing.
Tell you what,
let's take it one at a time.
You first. How did you get here?
I don't know.
I was drinking at a bar,
then someone started chasing me.
Then I passed out,
and woke up here.
I don't know anything.
I didn't do anything.
Alright.
Then what?
Then I have to beat you.
If I beat you, I can get out.
That's too bad.
You can't beat me.
I will win.
I told you, you can't beat me.
Look at you.
Even though I don't know how you won,
you definitely had people looking out for you.
Here's the deal,
Xie Xin.
I won't hit you. I won't hit you.
How about this, let me sum you up.
As for you...
If I say you're a good person,
you definitely aren't.
If I say you're a bad person,
you're not exactly bad either.
Of course, that's completely normal.
Because there are way too many people in this world
who are stuck somewhere between good and bad.
You know what your problem is?
You just love giving yourself an out.
You...
You've spoiled yourself rotten.
You completely coddle yourself, you know?
Why do you have so many reasons?
So many excuses?
Like you're the only one wronged.
Like you're always right.
You chose this path.
You said those words.
You did those things.
So just own up to it.
Right?
You probably don't understand anyway.
Tell you what,
while keeping our gloves
from touching each other,
stick out your right elbow.
That's it. Hook onto me.
Hook onto me.
Okay, ready to get up.
One, two, go.
Good work.
The match is over.
Both sides have equal points.
It's a joint victory.
Heart rate?
Heart rate is 45.
Heart rate is too low.
Blood oxygen level?
70.
Administer oxygen.
Okay.
Prepare an adrenaline shot.
Right away.
Start chest compressions.
Prepare for defibrillation.
Hurry!
Okay.
IV epinephrine, 0.5.
Confirmed. It's Xie Xin.
They're working on him right now,
but it's not looking good.
The family's been notified.
They should be here by now.
I'll... I'll keep watch a bit longer, okay?
I'll head back... head back later.
Zhang Ya.
I'm Shen Li.
Here.
This is his phone.
Thank you.
So you're the one who brought Xie Xin to the hospital.
Yeah, I just happened to see him having a heart attack.
It wasn't just a coincidence, was it?
Right.
Well...
Because our squad received a tip,
saying he...
saying, um...
someone was selling fake drugs at the bar.
So I...
Xie Xin once told me...
...that people want to say four things on their deathbed.
What four things?
I really want to know who he would say them to.
I'm looking for Grandpa Lin.
He doesn't work here anymore.
He handed this shop over to me.
I'm sorry.
Xie Xin.
Thank you.
I forgive you.
I love you.
Um, family of the patient...
It's all just a dream,
right?
Then I'll give you one last sweet dream.
Going all out
Equally matched